♪ In the not-too-distant future
♪ Somewhere in time and space
♪ Mike Nelson and his robot pals
♪ Are caught in an endless chase
♪ Pursued by a woman
whose name is Pearl
♪ An evil gal who
wants to rule the world
♪ She threw a few
things in her purse
♪ And in her rocket
ship she hunts him
♪ All across the universe
I'll get you!
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies
♪ The worst I can find,
la, la, la,
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ And I'll monitor his mind,
la, la, la,
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control
♪ Where the movies begin or end,
la, la, la,
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
♪ With the help of
his robot friends
♪ Robot roll call
♪ - Cambot
- you're on
♪ - Gypsy
- Oh my stars!
♪ - Tom Servo
- Check me out
♪ - Croooow
- I'm different
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♪ and other science facts,
la, la, la,
♪ Just repeat to
yourself it's just a show
♪ I should really just relax
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000
(clanging vibrations)
See what I mean?
Man, look at those things.
Do we tell him?
We have to.
Mike? Get in here, Mike.
Mike? Oh, there you are.
Hey guys.
Hi everyone, welcome to
the Satellite of Love.
Forget about that,
it's not important.
Mike, look at this.
Eew, yuck, what
are those things?
Those are eyelash mites.
They live in human eyelashes.
Yeah, you know,
I've heard of that,
it's a symbiotic thing where
they, little microscopic things
they feed off the dust and
debris of my eyelashes, yeah.
So you eat, and all
the food goes splashing
all over your face, and you
end up with monstrous demons
feeding off the garbage
dripping from your eyelashes.
And you're okay with that?
Well, I mean, if you
put it that way it doesn't
sound so great.
I'm sorry, they gotta
go, we have got to get rid
of these things.
You guys, they're
really very small.
Oh, they're small,
meaning we don't have to
concern ourselves with the
other helpless creatures
undoubtedly living
in your eyelashes,
whole villages of
tiny, big-eyed children
being devoured by these dragons.
Is that in the article?
Yeah, it is.
You know what?
He likes having eyelash
mites, he enjoys
having meats and eggs
and sauces and saliva
hanging from his eyelashes.
If you guys are that
concerned about it
we could probably have
the nanites, you know,
take a look at it.
Alright, I'll go
get the nanites.
Okay.
Is that big-eyed thing
in the article here?
'Cause I don't see that.
It might have been
another issue, I don't know.
("MST3K Love Theme" plays)
Never fear, Mike, the nanites'll
have those disease-ridden
little pests off of your
oil-soaked eyelashes in no time.
We're talking about a
little fracas here, right?
I mean, we're not talking about
a war or anything, are we?
No, no, no.
Well, well no, no, no, no, no.
Don't even say the
word "war", Mike.
We'll send in a few nanites
to act as a security force.
It'll really be more
like a police action.
It'll be more like we're
relocating your eyelash mites,
teaching them to live
somewhere better,
like on a dog's back or
the thigh of a squirrel.
Yeah.
Well if you guys
think my eyelashes
are really disgusting--
Oh, absolutely,
filthy, disgusting.
Well, let's have the
nanites take a look at 'em.
Alright, you're
gonna like it Mike.
Best thing that ever
happened to you, buddy.
Okay, nanites, are you
positioned on forehead ridge?
Sir, yes sir, troops
are in position.
Then if the weather
is right, initiate
Operation Gross Eye.
Sir, yes sir.
Let's rock and roll people.
Ooh, it is not going well.
Not well at all.
You gotta cut your
losses, Nelson.
Hello, hello?
We're getting cut to
shreds in there, man.
We can't win this war, they
know the eyelashes too well.
What kind of an animal
called this war anyway?
Who could have done this?
Who? Just tell me who?
(crying out)
Ned, Ned the nanite.
- Oh Ned!
- Ned! Ned!
Oh, Nelson, why did
you want this war?
What? Was it about pride?
Tell us.
What, me?
You're the ones who forced me--
Save it, butcher.
Pearl's calling.
Ah, there's the click.
Some say it's imbued with
the power of Zeus himself.
Whatever.
Say, make yourself useful
and hook me one of these.
Hey loser.
I found out that
Bobo is the Mad Goth
and he's like these
Spartan guys' big hero
'cause he can kill
lions and stuff,
like big whoop, who can't?
Now they're throwing a
big party in his honor
and people aren't paying
enough attention to me.
Are you talking to your
little gods in the sky
because no one else
will talk to you?
Slut, I mean, what?
(fanfare)
He's here!
The Mad Goth has arrived!
(applause)
Oh Cal, Cal, be a dear
and nip out for more mead.
But I'm doing
the statue thing.
More mead.
Yes dear.
Thank you, thank you,
well who's got it going on?
We believe that you do.
Aha, let me hear
it from you people.
We praise you and
we hold you high.
Aha, now that's what
I'm talking about.
Oh, I'm gonna be
ill, very, very ill.
Oh no, not the brain, oh please.
Oh, this is not good.
Though Nelson
promised a quick return
of the nanite forces,
the war for his eyelashes
lasted well into December.
Thousands were cut down
defending a blasted little patch
of Nelson's T-zone
known as Follicle Hill.
Would you guys knock it off?
I mean, you're the ones
who wanted this war anyway.
It's too late to
apologize now, Mike.
Right.
Hey, wait a minute, can't the
nanites just fix themselves?
Oh sure, no problem.
Well then what, ow, ow.
And in honor of
our beloved Mad Goth.
Thank you, thank you.
We unveil this 40-foot statue.
(awing and oohing)
Oh, look at the
definition, huh?
Could have used a little
more marble in there,
but still a
creditable effort, eh?
(clapping)
Well, come on everybody,
let's go watch me eat.
Oh, let's do, let's do.
Well there you have it then.
It's time, I think.
Lovely.
(singing)
No, Brain Guy, no!
No!
I'm using this!
Oh, no, no you're not.
Let's wait, Pearl.
Tempting as it is we must
delay our own suicides
and recapture Professor Bobo.
His reckless time
travel could rip apart
the universe itself!
So?
How to explain it
to the likes of you?
Okay.
Bobo ripples time itself,
the Nabisco company never
comes into being, no more
"Chicken In A Biskit".
Bobo's... messing... with my...
favorite... snack... cracker?
That's right.
Let's go.
Goddamn.
Oh, by the way, Mike,
Pearl told me to tell you
that your movie this week is
Invasion of the Neptune Men.
Enjoy.
See ya.
Eew.
Wow, jeez Mike, now your
eyes are a real mess.
Why'd you even get rid
of your eyelash mites?
You know, they're the things
that keep your eyelashes clean.
Oh, we've got movie sign, I'll
deal with you two later.
(clanging vibrations)
Hey, look at that,
it's Oliver Reed's liver
encased in Lucite.
Oh, it's kind of
a gentle invasion.
Yeah the kind of
invasion you can
listen to all day.
Well, kids, the Hamilton
clock on the wall
tells us it's time for the
Invasion of the Neptune Men.
Wow, they blew their wad
on the title sequence.
I used to be
virulently anti-pix,
but now I'm pro-pix.
Well, if it's not
too much trouble,
could somebody ritual
seppuku me right now, please?
Sounds like the Little Rascals
are gonna be in this.
This must be the
national anthem of Neptune.
Featuring Santa,
Speed Racer, Shonen Knife,
Sailor Moon!
Oh no, someone knocked
over the sump pump
in the Mir.
This is Runic two,
which reached the
moon the other day.
Oh, boy.
I wish I'd been on it.
You were on it, Mr.
Tabana, weren't you?
Of course he was.
He worked on it
with Dr. Strauss,
didn't you, Mr. Tabana?
Kid got off a good one, great.
D'oh! Now the Mir's fan
belt has snapped.
Pretty exciting, isn't it?
Sure is!
Well, children,
that ship was built
after Major Glenn's
spaceflight by Dr. Strauss
and Dr. Tanowei, Kenny's father.
Major Glenn and I
are to be married.
I merely assisted the others.
And worked on it.
Do you think you
and Kenny's father
can design a spaceship
all by yourselves?
Why, sure.
Ow, my spine!
A scientist like
Dr. Tanowei can,
Mr. Tabana is his right arm.
Isn't that so, sir?
No.
We can work together.
We're done, so you
can go out and play.
Go to Germany and play.
It's cram camp.
Come to the
Renaissance festival.
They're trying
to catch Mothra.
Strange way to dry your bowls.
10:26, it's time the
satellite got here.
Get moving, huh?
Okay.
Swing it over more.
Alright.
How fast is the wind blowing?
18 miles an hour.
Which way?
South-southeast.
Thank you for sewing
my hand to the tent.
Hey what is it?
Any sign of it yet?
Look at those two lovers.
Jeez, they're all
over each other.
No one looks down
for a satellite.
I got mixed up.
He's very young.
Yeah.
And he's Japanese.
Ooh.
I invite you to
pull my finger.
Hey, the satellite has fallen!
Huh, what?
I'm sure it's the satellite,
it landed in those woods.
Come on, let's go!
Head for the Alps,
the border is closed!
Music courtesy of
Sergei Prokofiev.
We feel fresh.
These kids are like 10, so.
Yeah, they're
well out of college.
Shouldn't they
be at their jobs, then?
Ah, ooh, ow, oh, the sawgrass,
oh why did I wear
my little shorts?
Soldiers are
popping up everywhere
asking if the war is over yet.
Wonder if he's
been lapped yet.
He's in there, over there!
There's no satellite here.
But I saw it!
It wouldn't come
down here, never!
He imagined it.
Yeah.
Look, that's it!
Hey come on let's go!
Oh, I can see how
they missed that.
Prefab Lutheran church.
Ah, Allegra.
A spaceship.
It's not Runic Two!
Come on, there never
were two ships on Earth.
Why did it fall down?
What next?
Get over there!
I wouldn't go.
Why not?
You found it, you know.
I'm too scared to go.
He must be the
Piggy of the group.
How do we pickle it?
Look at the size of it.
That part there is
how you get into it.
(cries out)
What's that?
Suppository Man.
Say, could you guys help me
get this thing off my neck?
Don't worry kids,
it's a promotional
gimmick for Sushi Cereal.
Oh, hi, say, we're
looking for the Bullethead
family reunion?
Go that way, no,
go over there, wait,
now you fall down, good.
Ah, Kenny, Kenny, Kenny!
(yelling)
We're on gool.
They have Braille helmets.
So the aliens
come and strangle
little kids.
Thank you, Japan.
Nice.
So they all die and
the movie's over.
Oh good, alright.
And immediately Bob Hope
is flown in to
entertain the troops.
Tojo's death car.
(mumbling)
Run, get out of here.
You're in my
pickled eel garden.
Get moving!
Come on, let's go!
Take us away, little shorts.
My baru barockers really work.
Ha ha ha ha ha, your costume
is ridiculous.
Children of the pot.
La Toya Jackson.
Ha ha! Oh, sorry, I missed.
Ah, this guy trained
under Bruce Lee... bowitz.
Ah, ah.
Oh that guy just fell down,
for crying out loud.
Ah, ah.
Waah.
Go Panthers!
Oh, I rode my
bike to work today.
This is the set of Tattletales,
if I'm not mistaken.
I just know Dr.
Smith's gonna be in this.
William.
Well, I checked,
there's no toilet paper
downstairs either.
We do have water
damage, don't we?
What the hell are
they doing out there?
I knew we shouldn't have
sent in the B-squad.
Jeez. Ronnie, Chad,
Bryce, get back in here.
They're being defeated
by a wispy bachelor.
A table saw on his head.
("MST3K Love Theme" plays)
Start the rockets
Ed, start the rockets!
Say, has anyone seen my record?
We gotta go in,
but we'll be back.
Legalize it.
Oh come on, I
wanna jump around
while you fall down more.
(mumbles)
Hey!
Oh, looks like the Russians
blew another reactor.
Yep.
(lightning striking)
Draw, storm.
What the hell'd I do that for?
Playing is hard today.
Fine, fine, we'll just invade
somewhere else then.
Did you, oh, sorry,
I thought you said something.
Finally, this movie is over.
Did this one seem
really long to you guys?
Actually, I don't
think it's over.
This is the Neptunian
Bay of Pigs.
(cheering)
Yay, they'll
park 10 miles away
and kill other people.
Grill's ready.
That's Space Chief.
Space Chief?
(cheering)
Hey, hey, hey,
don't touch the car.
Thanks a lot for saving
us, that was great.
The greatest.
Who are ya, mister?
Yeah, what's your name?
You boys picked one
that suits me fine.
Move back and let me go.
How 'bout ineffectual
chicken-headed bachelor?
Oh, boy.
He really cherried
out his golf cart.
Space Chief.
That's Space
Chief, and he's real.
Space Chief, guys, he's real!
He spins around
and strafes the kids.
Well, you know, it
wasn't really that bad.
At least it was short.
Am I supposed to eat this?
Oh father, can't you
take a rest and get to bed?
Where's Tabana?
He'll be coming soon.
I'm down 400 million yen.
What's your hurry, Papa?
Oh.
What times are it?
(giggles)
You're going to be sick.
That cold seems worse.
I must put on
something decent.
(knocking)
Hello.
See that wave band?
Something's happening
to make it reverse.
It's over 200 maaahs!
What is it?
Probably some upset caused
by the flight of a satellite.
An extraordinarily
strong electronic wave.
Our radar telescope
reported it, sir.
Our men have been
picking up the band.
On the scope, eh?
Yes.
It's ultra short.
66 mega cycles, sir,
on the band.
The opera?
And yet it measures
about 18,000 kilowatts.
The band's ultra short?
Where's it from, then?
Our electronic brain
stopped working immediately.
It just stopped?
Yeah.
Much like our scene.
Another celebrity interview?
Darn it, I just can't
get a news break,
there's nothing happening.
Well there's the
dolphin-killing festival.
What?
The clock's running backwards.
That means lunch
won't be 'til yesterday.
(beeping)
It must be Santa's beeper.
(dance music)
Meanwhile, in
pre-revolution Havana...
Is this what the
Japanese think we do?
Oh, it was such a great song.
Oh, let's go.
Hey, look.
Paul is a dead man,
miss him, miss him.
It's running backwards?
Who's been fiddling
around with this?
What kind of a
machine is this?
(beeping)
Not a very good
elk call, is it?
(singing)
That's weird, these
guys don't look Irish.
Hey, come on.
Did you leave a
yen on the track?
Do the Japanese practice
just in time railroad repair?
What's going on?
That engineer's crazy.
He's crazy.
What's he trying to do, crash?
Japan's only stupid guy.
(beeping)
Take over the
administration building.
What happened to
reverse the current, sir?
Electrically operated industries
said their power failed.
All our town sent in reports.
And that queer sound.
An American satellite, one
might have been overhead.
I will not answer that
until we have investigated.
Doctor, this is not
a natural phenomenon.
A strong electronic
wave of unknown origin
did put our power supply
temporarily out of order.
Am I right?
I'd say that you're correct.
Papa, space men,
we saw a whole bunch!
Really, and their
rocket ship, teacher!
It's different than
the Runic, honest!
Get the cane.
Where was this, son?
Out near Mount Asaka.
We were there to
see the satellite.
Well?
We were caught
by the space men.
But Space Chief
came and saved us.
Huh?
Space Chief, huh?
We named him, he's the
greatest, the real thing.
He got there in seconds.
Space Chief, eh?
A fighter?
Yeah, we'll make
it a feature story.
We told you the truth.
Pencil drop.
10 o'clock.
Well, back to the
national emergency, okay?
Dr. Tanowei, how do
you see these things?
As scientific phenomena?
Tell us sir,
what's causing them?
Randy?
We knew you'd listen.
You understand.
Hey, that's a good one.
Voices.
Tabana, I can see
you're not taking
all this space talk
seriously, are you?
Well, it's an
interesting idea.
Look Tabana.
What's going on?
The power plant failed,
everything's stopped.
You see, you
know who did that?
Well, here's your news break.
Take those kids
out to Mount Asaka.
Leave 'em.
Get a shot of
whatever's there.
It's nonsense, you know that.
Why not?
Will you kids take
him out there?
Sure, come on, we'll show him.
How'd they ever get around
to designing good cars?
I don't know.
(clanging vibrations)
Hello and konichiwa.
Tonight we present a traditional
Japanese kabuki play.
Translated to English, this
ancient work is entitled
Neil Simon's
"The Sunshine Boys".
Now, how many of you are
familiar with Japanese theater?
Anyone wanna field this one?
Anybody at all.
Ah, yes sir.
And do you enjoy kabuki theater?
Actually I prefer noh theater.
Well then why did
you raise your hand?
Because I like noh theater.
Noh plays are my favorite.
So you don't like
any theater at all.
No, let me explain.
Noh theater is classic
Japanese drama.
Noh plays have been produced
since the 13th century
and noh actors are
revered even today.
Why are you dissing
Japanese theater?
What's your deal, man?
No, no, wait a minute.
Noh theater started in Japan.
Oh, so now you tell
us Japan doesn't have
any theater whatsoever.
They have lots of theater
including noh theater.
So they have lots of theater
and they have no theater.
- Exactly.
- What?
- No theater?
- Yes.
What?
- Noh theater, N-O-H.
- N-O-H, huh?
Well there, you've just gone and
shown what an idiot you are!
Hey, I'll handle
this Tom, calm down.
Mike, I'm going to ask you
a series of simple questions
which even a cretin like
you could answer yes or no.
Now, is there theater in Japan?
Yes.
Good.
And do you have a
particular favorite type of
Japanese theater?
Yes.
Well, good, now we're
getting somewhere.
Mike, will you tell me the
name of your favorite form
of Japanese theater?
Noh.
- Why not?
- Why not what?
Why won't you tell me your
favorite Japanese theater?
- I just did!
- Did what?
Told you my favorite
form of Japanese theater.
You did?
Yes.
Well, will you tell me again?
Yes, noh.
Oh come on!
Mike, I'm gonna
grab a step ladder
so you can jump up my butt.
May we do our little
kabuki play now?
Go ahead but remember
I like noh theater
more than I like kabuki theater.
I thought you
didn't like kabuki!
I don't.
(crying)
You gotta mess with
'em every now and then.
We'll be right back.
I get it Mike.
("MST3K Love Theme" plays)
Noh theater, gee.
Ah, the camera's going
up, it's the end, alright!
D'oh.
Scientists labor to find out
what the hell is
the deal with Japan.
I can only fake
it for so long.
Have we solved love yet?
Tabana, there's that
electronic wave again.
Oh.
What is the band?
It's Rip Taylor's
voice pattern.
Charlie was close, he
was right next to me.
It's my line, right?
Hmm.
What?
I'm hungry.
Why, it's sigma electrowave.
What's this sigma?
We really know
very little about it.
It's an ultra short wave
we can't record on Earth.
Attention, will
Mr. Tabana please
report to Dr. Tanowei's office?
Will Mr. Tabana please report
to Dr. Tanowei's office?
At the Comfort Inn Suites.
No one showed up
for my one-man Il Duce show.
Yes sir?
A telegram.
It was delivered
on the balcony.
From Mount Wilson
Observatory in California.
The band was
caught in America?
In Big Pink?
Doctor, down in the
lab we caught it again.
We're sure about it, it's sigma.
You know sir, I think
that wave is being
transmitted into
space from the Earth.
You have shamed me by
losing track of the band.
You see, the space men,
who are still close to us,
are transmitting it now.
Do you know where
it's coming from?
My hair, sir.
And it won't be very easy.
Looks like they're
using unknown material
that's blurring our radar.
Hmm.
That caused today's
power failure.
They might take over
the entire Earth.
Entire?
Doctor, you are
planning to announce this?
I will not.
Bye now.
Why not?
We're in dire peril.
What will the
future hold for us?
Tabana.
There's a chance
your guess is right
and the space men are on Earth.
You jerk.
But our only proof
is the sigma wave band
and that won't tell
us where they are.
We are scientists, not prophets.
An announcement
could start a panic.
I am so a prophet.
Ah, we shall get the truth.
Let us just work hard together.
We have our electro barrier.
We will try to bring it off.
We'll beat 'em.
Good, now scram, big hair.
What I don't like
is they're trying
to bring about unrest by
causing unusual phenomena
instead of attacking
us directly.
I see that we face
a dangerous enemy.
Wow, what a view.
So, jump then, or...?
Walter Mondale goes camping.
It's not a very
good combine, is it?
Hey, this isn't Squid World.
This is it, right here.
Okay, where's the
spaceship around here?
I don't see any.
That's funny.
This place looks too clean.
Maybe they came back.
Do you think so?
I don't know.
Perhaps you're correct.
They cleared
away their tracks.
Say, have you
got an imagination.
It's true, they
were here, honest.
I know, like your Space Chief.
Come on, I heard it all before.
He did come here too.
Don't break me up, I
gotta take a picture.
Okay.
Set the stop at five six.
Move over.
Look.
Kurosawa, eat your heart out.
Okay, let's go home.
I gotta get my
little shorts too.
What is it?
You go, we'll stay
and look around.
It'll be too dark.
Don't worry, you
guys stick around.
We'll stay.
Look, I'll go then, okay?
Don't play too long.
Okay.
Boy that guy really
photojournalisted
the hell out of that place.
Sure did.
What's this?
It isn't any rock.
What is it?
Hey, look at this, it flashed
when that bulb went off.
Part of the ship you think?
Yeah, Space Chief shot
at 'em, and this must have
come off.
Is there any shame
we can attach to it?
It's so light!
Yet filling.
Tabana's the one who'll know.
Come on, let's go.
They were never seen again
and Japan came to
an end, the end.
Why did I buy a ride
for my living room?
Hi.
The guy at the desk
said it was urgent.
Got my porn bill.
Is that really
what I look like?
So what?
You explain it.
Your spaceship landed there.
Oh, my spaceship.
When we bought it, it
was our spaceship.
That shiny object.
I'd like to put it in my nest.
Does it back up those
kids or doesn't it?
Now what do you think?
Can't tell.
I must look into it
all properly first.
You think that shiny
spot in the picture
has some scientific
significance, then?
Where is this object?
About where the
kids showed us.
I'm not sure it's out there yet.
We'll see.
(kids clamoring)
Apparently the
kids have level five
security clearance.
Let's see that.
It belongs to
the spaceship, sir.
If you test that,
will it prove that
the space men are here?
Perhaps. I'll do a test now.
(explosion)
Ooh, grandpa tried
to program his VCR.
The reactor, they
blowed up our reactor.
Ah, the mosquito
spraying program
is off to a great start.
Suppose Rachel Carson's
gonna bitch about this now.
Our largest nuclear reactor
exploded at 5:20 p.m. yesterday.
84 people are dead.
This board concludes
that artificial phenomena
have been caused by
an unknown aggressor
flying high enough to
avoid radar detection.
And yet we play Rack-O.
This aggressor has beamed
down an ultra short wave band
that has neutralized
our power stations.
It is obvious that
the suspect country is
undoubtedly the one which
now possesses the first
spaceship large
enough to do this.
Now, who wants dessert?
Since Dr. Tanowei who
heads our science laboratory
is ill today, Mr. Tabana,
his assistant, will now give
his opinion of the situation.
♪ Can't get enough of
Super Sugar Crisp...
Then I must say I reject
your last statement.
I'm sure no country
upon this planet
neutralized our power plants.
Whatever that means.
Can you explain that?
I understand some
young schoolchildren
have seen a spaceship.
The information is carried
in today's newspaper.
Oh and don't miss
Dilbert today, it's great.
Yes, Senator, go on.
I cannot believe that
our friend here is serious.
All countries are in
grave danger, gentlemen,
and this is hardly the
time to be influenced
by fairytales that have no
basis in scientific fact.
I'd like the know the facts.
Sorry, I was in the weeds.
Did Joanie come by with menus?
Mr. Gower's son died.
This cable was just received.
It says "Cause unknown as
yet, but our nuclear reactor
"has just exploded."
The message is from
the United States.
I agree with our president,
it's time we took action.
They'll never know
we're pirating cable.
Why should we be
afraid of one another?
Oh, grown ups have no sense.
Do you think they're
gonna start a war then?
The space men sure want to.
They're doing it.
They want the Earth.
When the earthlings are dead,
the space men will take over.
(beeping)
His glasses'll be
done in about an hour.
♪ Set me free why
don't you, babe.
Just a quick peek at porn.
Sea monkeys are disappointing.
So, then.
The Roji-Pani complex.
The Roji panty complex?
Neptune, right?
Their ships, they
use those elements.
Roji panty complex.
("MST3K Love Theme" plays)
Hey, it's Thomas
the Tank Spaceship.
And I hope that
commencing our fight
all countries will cease
suspecting their brothers
and pitch their energies
against our attackers.
Where is my record?
And there is no need
to despair as yet.
Okay, now despair.
To hearten you, I
will tell you this.
Our international space
science laboratory
has sufficient electro
barriers and indeed we must--
Am I the only
one working here?
Hello?
Prepared to fight
with the human race
for the human race, the Neptune
plan to conquer the Earth
is doomed to failure.
Oh, what a great
turkey dinner.
You gals get to
working on the dishes,
I'm gonna have a sit down.
Okay guys, let's
lay down that lead
guitar track just one more time.
Shoot at Earth all you want,
just get Bill Maher.
- Yeah.
- Jeez, Midasize it.
You know it was a new record,
I just bought it, you know.
This spaceship
is powered by coal.
Are we gonna put in
a table leaf or not?
Doctor, tell us
this, will you please?
Just what does the
electro barrier do?
I brought this chart along.
Look, gentlemen.
The electro barrier sets
up a dome of electrons
completely covering
any city beneath it.
If it's really tiny.
We turn on the power and
no one can pierce our shield?
Look, we'll explain.
Every city can be amply
protected by its own power dome.
A baked potato?
So each power dome
covers a small area.
Like mine.
Are you saying that
nobody can get through that?
Good serve.
It depends on just
what they're using
when they attack us.
Quite a volley.
But do we have power?
Yes, we have.
They're working very
hard to set it up today.
Well, tomorrow,
I think they're
taking a day off.
The spaceship,
it's coming back,
they're going to attack us.
What can we do?
Will the barrier protect us?
We just threw it
together, I mean.
Operator, get me
a line into seven.
Apparently seven's
an old locker room.
Doctor, the
barrier is operating.
Certainly.
Generating power is 300
million electronic volts,
height: 500 miles.
Is it an attack?
Hear anything?
Can they trust that barrier?
(laughs)
That kid.
You bet.
I'm not scared.
If the barrier fails, Space
Chief'll beat 'em again.
He sure will.
Meanwhile, in a hideous little
simulacrum of the
United States...
Gamera, get back
in your kennel.
(sirens)
Run!
Riot, loot,
burn down the Asian
grocery stores!
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
All the streetlights are out.
Gee, it's dark down there.
There's no light anywhere
except the barrier station.
Let's go there and annoy 'em!
Ah, look at that!
A spaceship!
Days later, during an average
Tokyo shopping day...
Giant flying short grain rice.
Oh, Jimmy Osmond
and Santa, save us!
On the left, it's
John Foster Dulles.
They're attacking St. Louis.
Desk job chief.
Oh, it's Mr. Bill, oh no.
Guys, come on,
where's my record?
I mean it, it's not funny
anymore, I spent a lot
for that record,
where'd you put it?
Hey, Phil, now you were a big
Loggins and Messina fan.
Phil.
Future cities of the past.
By Kenner.
Say, Smitty, you
wanna grab this?
I wanna take my smoke break.
Thanks.
Maybe we all shouldn't have
quit caffeine at the same time.
Oh, didn't mean to do that,
just wanted to turn
up the heat, sorry.
And the angel
Gabriel's in the lead,
along the rail St.
Michael's in second,
there's a pack of cherubim
and seraphim closing in fast.
(explosion)
Get under the table!
Move over, Bernard Shaw.
Yay.
Portfolio's gaining
by the moment.
My head is a Koosh ball.
I hate living
near the airport.
It's the aliens!
I'm scared.
Me too.
So they glued wings
to a fuel filter.
No, not Betty Tech Com Corp.
Oh man, and they just
got ISO 9001 certified.
I'm losing weight
as we invade,
thanks to my new sauna suit.
Intergalactic flaming jarts.
Oh, they're invading
Buckminster Fuller's
geodesic dome city.
Stop zooming in,
I have no emotions
to show you.
The first version of Pac-Man
wasn't very much fun.
The washer is off-balance.
Our office furniture!
Our honeycombs!
So the things
are doing things.
I guess.
A breakdancing task chair.
They're making the
chicken men of Krankor
look super confident
and dignified.
Dammit, I am trying to make
a sandwich here!
So it turns out
that the aliens
are a big bunch of pussies.
Thank God.
And his son, Santa Claus.
(cheering)
Yay, a dot is moving away
from a semi-circle, yay.
Hooray for the
electro barrier.
Hooray for Mr. Tabana!
Whoever he is, yeah.
The lights are going
on again, hooray!
Hooray, hooray, hooray.
Well, it really does work.
Yes, what a victory
for the scientific world.
You bet.
Where's Tanowei?
I guess he left.
Hey, did you see that ship run?
Help, I'm right here, help.
So Dr. Tanowei, you
don't think the spaceship
has left us for good.
No Professor Froggy.
I think not sir.
The Earth can almost certainly
count on several more
such attacks.
But can the electro barrier
continue to protect us
in that case?
Of course, General.
You saw yourself
how effective it is.
Yes, the electro
barrier is good,
but it will not aid us in
attacking those creatures.
True, sir, and further,
there is not one weapon
we could win this fight with.
I fear you will have
to try and invent it.
The hard way.
We have found Rojium
and Panium in there.
There it is again, panty.
Plus alpha electron
is also there.
I'd like to launch missiles
with electron minus alpha
in their warheads.
I'm feeling kinda...
You alright?
Attract the missile
and be exploded.
I think it could work well.
Or well-ish.
And yet, it would cause
severe damage when it struck
the Earth if it were to
fall in a civilian area.
We might all take shelter
or guide the ship to sea.
Or run away in a
panicky mob as usual.
In any case, let us
please act quickly.
I don't think I
can, carry me out.
Let me take a look at you.
What's going on?
You alright?
Is over.
The right shorts.
I'll handle it, guys.
("MST3K Love Theme" plays)
Shh, you'll be okay.
I'm afraid Servo has
contracted Roji panty complex
so I'm administering
panties to him.
I think he's gonna
make it, but--
More panties, Mike, I
need another four-pack.
Servo, your body can only
absorb so many panties per hour.
Please.
Why don't we check what's
going down on the planet, okay?
Let's check, shh.
(snoring)
Bobo, Bobo!
Well, hello bush.
No, you idiot, it's us.
Well, hello other bush.
Say, do you little
bushes want an autograph?
Well, come back for
the autograph session.
Listen you simian
moron, it's--
Flavia, the talking
bushes are annoying me!
(shushing)
And now they're hitting me, too!
And now they're trying to
muffle my screams, Flavia!
Bobo, it's me, Pearl!
Oh, hello, who's
the dead fellow?
No you clod, it is your old
friends Pearl and Observa,
and you do not live in
ancient Rome and you are not
some Mad Goth and until
two weeks ago you were
traveling with us through
time and space when
you fell into a worm
hole, do you remember?
I tell you, that could be.
The fact is I got so
much water in the brain
from lions cuffing me
in the noggin you could
be absolutely right.
Alls I know is I got a statue.
Grape?
Look Bobo, you
have to come with us.
Someone's coming,
someone's coming.
God I love grapes.
A grape and a statue,
that's all I need.
Oh, esteemed Mad Goth,
did I hear you yelling at me
about talking bushes?
Oh, it turns out
that they're very nice.
Oh, because sometimes
when the bushes talk
it means they need pruning!
Gods, what a surprise.
Sometimes when you're
a god you have to just
inspect the bushes
every now and then.
(muttering)
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm administering
panties to Servo.
He's got Roji panty complex.
I got it too, Mike.
Apply panties to me,
I've got it real bad.
It's too late,
we've got movie sign!
You go ahead, I'll be along.
(clanging vibrations)
Thank you Mike.
I don't feel very
good, I'm telling you.
Hi.
How are the discoverers
of the space men?
You're heroes, you know.
Yesterday you laughed at us
and today we're all heroes.
Now you're gonna
take a beating.
Which side are you on?
We're pretty mad.
Sure are.
Sorry guys, we're
idiots, I guess.
That's right, and
don't forget it.
You're lucky, you
should have been fired.
You get your pay, you've had it.
Oh, brother.
So, general psychoses
and freakiness all around, huh?
It's Roji panty complex, Mike.
Good morning, hello!
Hi there.
Say, sir, wasn't
that the greatest?
And the barrier did it!
That's a neat trick.
Boy, just like rabbits, huh?
Yeah, you said it.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah.
Kenny, and you too,
we are trying to have
a little privacy.
Right.
But we're Japanese children,
we can go anywhere
we want at any time.
That's right.
Listen, what are they talking
about in there, do you know?
I'm afraid it's
not for children.
Yeah, get her.
She was shaking like
a leaf yesterday.
Stop it.
(laughing)
Be ashamed of your womanness.
Guys, I'll show you something.
Okay, yeah, what?
Shorts you can tattoo on.
What is it, what do you got?
See this stick?
It's really something big.
It's Crystal
Gayle's curling iron.
It's a radar.
Oh.
Try it on this.
Yeah, try it, let's
see how it works.
Robby the Robot in
a depressing cameo.
- Wow.
- A short range radar.
Oh, it was made in America,
what a piece of junk.
Where did you get it?
Dr. Johnson gave it to me.
(chattering)
Here, use this.
Okay, hold it.
That'll have to
pass for fun for now.
Oh, look over there.
Another country,
that looks great.
Gee, look at that thing.
Hey, the barrier
station's under there.
It's a Christmas
ornament from the '60s.
Is it radar?
With Gary Burghoff?
Let's have a look.
Okay, yeah, let's go!
Radar.
Sewage plant is such
a fun place to play.
Guys, do we have to do
everything in a group?
Kill the pig, drink his blood!
Oh wait, that's another story.
Oh no, you kids again?
Is there anyone
else on this planet?
Look out!
It's a nauseating
shorts detector!
(monkey sounds)
Gee, it's funny looking.
Smaller than us,
we can torment it.
What do you think it is?
Maybe the space men sent it.
I think the Tin
Man had that thing
surgically removed.
Be careful.
It looks dangerous.
(beeping)
Oh, it's an individual
shrimp barbecue.
We'd better take it to
the laboratory right away.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Hey guys, can we
just walk to the lab?
It's just that I
have a heart murmur
and I'm not supposed to
run everywhere, oh boy.
Is he dead, what?
Isn't it about
time for a big old
Russian dance about now?
Hey, they found something.
What's that noise?
I don't know, come on.
(chattering)
Well I was attending
to the defense of the world,
but yeah, kids, I'll
look at your little toy.
He looks like the
Grinch, doesn't he?
How many cycles
in the sigma again?
Let's see now, 66 mega cycles.
My current
estimate is (mumbles)
Try it backwards.
The forces of
the planet Neptune
send this communique to
the people of the Earth.
James Earl Jones.
Your electro barrier
has driven back
our spaceship.
I'm sorry, I have a cold.
Rest assured, however,
that your triumph
is only temporary.
Don't worry.
You cannot defeat
the planet Neptune.
I won't hurt you.
Even while you listen to this
we are approaching Earth again.
And this time, your
childish electro barrier
will not be able to protect you.
I buried Paul.
A few short hours from now,
we shall take over your world.
That is all, hold on, wait.
Oh, Ted wants me to call
you a bunch of wieners.
Lieutenant, warn the
crew at the barrier.
Yes sir.
The two of you,
you'll both go.
Right.
And woman, you let
the kids mock you.
(muttering)
Please report to the
laboratory at once.
Those smelly stupid reporters
are on their way up.
A mega radar has picked up
the spaceship again.
Let's get out of
this movie, step on it!
I'm done degrading
this woman, who's next?
Where are they, exactly?
At present they're
150,000 miles out
and heading straight for us.
Do I have time to hit the loo?
And their speed?
50,000.
Doctor, when
will they reach us?
Doctor, when will they arrive?
Do they have an appointment?
On that orbital path,
I'd say about 12:30
they will reach the
city or be near it.
Is the barrier ready?
The barrier will be ready.
Alerting us to the danger
means they're pretty sure
of themselves.
What countermeasures
can they have?
Are we safe?
My friends, it's war.
We will use our brains
as well as our skill
against the enemy.
Grinch, it's the Grinch.
You must have faith.
Um, excuse me, I'm saluting.
Oh, don't say hi then,
that's fine, sure.
There appears to
be plenty of parking
for Lilith Fair.
Shall we?
It says, Bureau of Conformity.
Wow, they love their
collector's plates here.
The MTV News thing is broken.
Good.
The interior of a suitcase or
what, what are we seeing here?
The Japanese army
plays freeze tag.
Corn dogs, cold
beer, corn dogs.
I take my own personal
septic tank to work.
And he bought a
stainless steel brassiere
from this man.
Oh, I'm missing my story.
The Department of Children
is staffed round the clock.
I'm looking for dignity,
but there just isn't any.
And she was caught
in a vat of Jell-O
with these men.
Surely Mozart and
his holy reindeer
will come down to save us.
Well, if it's gonna
rain, it's gonna rain,
not much we can do about it.
Bars? What, does a
gorilla live up there?
I can't find it.
Where has that ship gotten to?
And that Ernie
and Uncle Charlie,
where have they gone to?
Playing an intense game
of red rover, red rover.
The significance of 20 to 1
can't be overstated.
Anything yet?
Not yet.
I hope we're ready.
We are, and we got Space
Chief on our side, see?
You wanna watch
it on the screen?
Yeah, sure, come on.
Oh no wait, my
shorts locked up.
Can't, oh there we go.
Nothing yet.
Oh, look at that.
What, where?
Oh it's a tire fire
that's been burning
for days, I just noticed it.
Come quickly, look, look.
A dust cloud.
What's that?
It's a dust cloud.
What do you mean?
What do you see?
Look at that.
Chris Farley broke wind.
Oh no.
The Stay Puft Marshmallow Boy.
Look at that.
(singing)
It's the AP wire service
cross country team.
They're like a
herd of whitetails,
they scare real easy.
A very average
summer storm is coming.
I am ashamed that
there is a storm over us.
Take positions, squad, to
your posts on the double!
But I just ordered a brat.
Let's find the children,
they'll know what to do.
Wow, location
scout for this movie
must have been a
manic depressive.
Designed by I.M. Pei,
built by Jim Varney.
Doctor, this storm may
damage the electro barrier.
I want them to deactivate it.
Yes, sir.
Stanley, get
everyone in here fast.
Ask me about my grandchildren.
Attention all
laboratory personnel
and members of the press.
Get to the shelters in
the basement immediately.
This is a red alert,
repeat, a red alert.
You're dead, red alert.
Better get in, huh?
Yeah, come on.
Take shelter!
But eat all you take!
Inside!
It's Thor.
I think they're
trying to pass off
a summer shower as an
action sequence here.
Yeah, that's what going on.
What the?
A Japanese clown tree.
Oh you never would believe
where those little
soldiers come from.
(howling)
Sir, can the security
guard be dismissed?
Yes, Captain.
Yes, I'd say his
opinion doesn't matter,
dismiss him completely.
All clear!
Listen to them
shout all clear.
Damn, they're good men.
♪ It's been a hard day's night
No, wait, let's
check the station.
You're right, they'll
attack us there.
Get going!
Yes, field marshal child.
And now a brief
musical tribute
to Alexander Nevsky.
You know, I wish the
running would never stop.
I mean, it, I simply
can't get enough shots
of these kids running.
Really, literally
there's no limit
to how much I want to see of it.
Just a little
sarcastic maybe, Mike?
Just a touch.
Oh no, I have trench mouth.
Wait, I'm better now.
♪ When Debbie comes
marching home again
♪ Hurrah, hurrah
♪ We'll give her a
panty girdle then
♪ Hurrah
Say.
Wait.
You guys pick me
up a pita pocket?
Halt, you there, halt!
(gunshots)
(cries out)
Why don't you swing
in here with me,
I gotta renew my license tabs.
Corporal, I can
see your panty lines.
Roji panty complex.
Sergeants Gladys and Peggy.
Thank God they carry
Clinique at the PX, eh?
Ready?
And strike, pout, put it out.
Kids must be in great shape.
That's funny, I
don't see any guards.
Where'd they go?
I don't know, Rocky.
There they are.
Hi, you guys.
Filmed in the ghetto
of Kingston, Jamaica?
It's a bad time of
month to mess with us.
They're here!
Run!
A tiny stick, no!
Cancel the invasion!
Yay, here come
the Banana Splits!
Hey, it's Space Chief.
Space Chief!
Space Chief, he's
running over us, alright!
I'll get him.
This gun has the power
to put their uniforms
back on.
We didn't get
shot but we're gonna
die anyway.
Space Chief is
actually Racer X,
Speed's brother.
(cheering)
Tear him up, rip him apart!
Quick, Space Chief,
two of them got into
the barrier station,
they're inside there now!
They all have
Flintstones phone voices.
Come on, let's watch.
Exit, stage left even.
It's the Keystone Kids.
(explosion)
Wow, big old space beef.
Get off me, Hideo.
Fresh blackfin tuna.
Ow, ow, ow, somebody
put wasabi in our jocks.
- Stanley.
- Yes, Ollie?
Are you kids alright?
Space Chief rescued us.
He went in there, Space
Chief is still inside.
Look at that!
You think he could have
gotten out of there somehow?
Come quickly!
The tampon machine is empty!
Stanley, the doctor's ill.
What's happened?
Tanowei, what's happened?
He's ill?
Why he should be ashamed.
Very dishonorable.
Doctor child arrives.
Kenny.
(mumbles)
RuPaul?
What's he got, Jimmy?
Boogie fever.
Electronic shock, apparently.
Causes unconsciousness.
("MST3K Love Theme" plays)
Yes?
Oh, one minute.
For you.
Some guy says your
inflatable doll's
on back order.
(shushing)
Captain speaking.
Oh, yes sir.
Power room is destroyed.
My paneling shrunk
and I'm upset.
Tanowei?
Is he very ill?
Watch him.
That guy can't
stop lathing, can he?
You guys wanna panic
in a tightly packed group later?
And this is our
best water softener,
but let me show you some of
the other models over here.
Hornet's nest
up there, see it?
We bring you now
to Brule, Wisconsin.
Hey look out, look out!
Walter Mondale
stops for chicken.
The catacombs of
ancient Legoland.
Yeah, if you want some candy,
just pull it off the wall.
Don't get up.
Hello.
Are the alpha electron
rockets ready?
Yes, they are sir.
Well, basically.
Where is this spaceship now?
The radar here
can't locate it,
but the omega radar in the
laboratory should have it.
I'll call there.
Calling there, actual footage.
Yes, we can't get it on radar.
We think it's already
landed in the suburbs.
What's happening?
The weather change?
Okay.
Fine.
There's an unusual
weather change.
The temperature started
going down suddenly.
Oh, and Deb says hi.
Tabana, the rockets.
You'll do it?
Yes.
John Sununu has that
waiting at all times.
I love those.
Timely joke.
Oh, London too?
And in Paris?
So long, pal.
Pal?
Temperatures are
dropping all over the world!
In Europe also?
The spaceship's landed,
we're sure they're causing it.
The jerks.
If this continues, the
entire Earth could freeze.
Another glacial age.
Yeah.
Hey look, it's snowing!
Yeah, he's right.
(cheering)
They're ogling
the Diet Coke guy.
This is not virtual.
Snow now really is weird.
I wonder why.
Who knows?
It is very unusual.
Yeah.
Weather like this,
there's something up.
Unbelievable, they've managed
to make the movie
more irritating.
(record skipping)
Go ahead and take it
to the bridge now,
take it to the bridge.
Sure they did, who
else caused this snow?
Can't they fight
them at least?
Space Chief is
the guy they need.
We must leave our pueblo.
If it gets any colder, we'll
freeze to death by night.
Look, the thermometer,
it's rising.
It is, it's going up!
Why do we all live
together with no adults?
Guys, come here
and take a look.
What's up?
Hey, the snow's stopping.
The sun, yay!
Our quick and pointless
plot cul-de-sac is over.
They say space men
caused all that snow.
I heard.
Anything can happen these days.
Oh.
Can't the government
do something?
They should, and soon, too.
We're all in great danger.
Yeah, I heard the electro
barrier was destroyed.
Attention all citizens.
The president of the
international defense board
is about to make an
important announcement.
Will you all please stay near
your television and radio sets?
Ladies and gentlemen.
The unusual weather
changes that occurred here
have also been occurring
throughout the entire world.
Jacques Cousteau.
They were caused
by the weather
control equipment operating
from the Neptune spacecraft.
Fortunately, their plan
to destroy the human race
by lowering the
temperature of our planet
was foiled by the electro
barrier which they tried
to blow up.
Um, yay?
However, we felt
we had reason--
To invade Manchuria.
So we got there before
they could find our barrier.
We have put it in an
underground laboratory
where it will continue
to protect us all.
(cheering)
I also invite
you to the caning
of five children.
The electro
barrier is covering
the entire metropolitan area
and has been able to
neutralize the cold
by sending out waves
of intense heat.
At the same time this
has brought about
a dangerous situation since
the spaceship is trapped
within the barrier.
At the moment, we cannot predict
what the space men will do
in their efforts to escape.
Pat Paulsen.
The defense board
is now proclaiming
a state of martial law
and orders all citizens
to take shelter in the country.
Transportation facilities
are now available.
All persons are to
leave the city at once
from assigned
transport stations.
But how much are
the oscillating fans?
(clamoring)
Attention, attention.
Um, let's see.
I forgot what I was
gonna say, I'm sorry.
Run, work, run
faster, work harder,
abandon healthy
diets, drink a lot,
never speak to your children,
do not apologize for the war!
- Do not panic.
- Yeah, right.
Find your transport station.
Make your way quietly to
your assigned station.
Do not panic.
Evacuate now.
Please do not panic!
Do not panic.
At least panic in
your pre-designated
subgroups.
Our virtual pets have turned
on us, they're attacking!
Patients are evacuated
from the center
for blowfish poisoning.
That trip to Six
Flags is still on,
bring a sack lunch.
Whatever happened to
that guy, Space Chef?
Chief.
Chief Chef, what?
No, Space Chief.
Oh.
The aliens are
terrified of themselves,
panic and leave immediately.
You know it seems weird,
but this movie was
based on a lyric poem
called "Lotus Wind Flower".
Sounds beautiful.
Miyashi told me I
look like a walrus.
Get ready, the spaceship
has just been launched.
Right.
Lower the barrier.
We must be crazy to
have a barrier this low.
Oh man, there
are 73 McDonald's
lawsuits pending.
Going down slowly, it's okay.
This movie is a Space
Chef vehicle, isn't it?
Chief, Chief, and yes.
What's the maximum?
Is there a point
that's dangerous?
6,000.
Then it's risky and
you take a chance.
A winged Playtex nurser.
Most like mother herself.
I'm gonna ramp
up the fuzz pedal
a little there for you.
Drop the pizzas,
drop the pizzas,
make the cheese really
hot and drop the pizzas!
Hold it.
Something's happened.
Yeah, right.
They've launched
two small spaceships.
The bearing is X326, Y275.
Bearing X326, Y275.
Why not 275?
Still heading south.
New bearing.
X69, y829.
This movie broke me,
Mike, I can't take it.
I know, I know, it's okay.
(clanging vibrations)
I mean, we've had bad movies
before, Mike, but this one.
I know Tom, I know.
My will to live, Mike,
draining, draining fast.
To be dead, to be nothing,
to watch Neptune Men no more.
I can't go back in, you guys,
shove me out the airlock,
please, Mike, if you have
a shred of decency left in you.
Oh, will there ever be
light in this world again?
I don't know
Tom, I don't know.
Whoever it is, go away!
Save yourself.
It is you who needs saving.
For you see our technology
is far superior to yours,
and we will crush you.
It's the phantom
dictator of Krankor
from Prince of Space, Krankor!
Yes it is I, and as you
can see I have come back
to conquer your puny
satellite once and for all.
(laughing)
Oh, God, it is good to see you.
Krankor, what a breath
of fresh air you are.
You guys it's really him,
it's really Krankor, hooray!
I do not understand.
Last time you did not seem
to like me very much at all.
No, no, no, Krankor,
don't say that.
That was before this
horrible movie we have today.
I think we've
learned to appreciate
what we had with you guys.
Well, that's, that's
very nice I suppose.
Wait.
(laughing)
Hooray.
Oh, God.
So Krankor, how are you man?
I suppose that I am fine.
Well, you been
keeping busy and all?
Yes, I have been working hard.
I suppose that one could say
that I am hardly working.
(laughing)
I love this man!
Hey Krankor, any good stories
about filming Prince of Space?
Yes, oh yes, well
there was this one time
I was supposed to walk
over to the X radar screen,
and I walked over to the
laser cannon panel instead.
No!
Quite an embarrassing
moment, as you might imagine.
(laughing)
Oh God, that's great, oh God.
Oh Krankor, God it's
good to see you.
Well it is good
to see you as well.
I guess my bellicose
ways prevent me from
expressing my
affection completely
but I see them now as a cover
for my loneliness at heart.
Well you're always welcome
here, friend, always.
Thank you, that's
very, that's very nice.
(crying)
You scum!
(laughing)
You're great, man. You the bird!
Oh yeah.
Well I suppose the Earth is
not going to conquer itself,
I better get, well.
No, it's not.
Goodbye, goodbye.
Bye Krankor.
Oh and by the way
it's useless to resist
for we will soon
conquer you completely.
(laughing)
We love you.
You've conquered my heart.
Oh, man.
God, that Krankor.
You feeling better Tom?
Oh, a lot better Mike, you
know, after a movie like this
to check in with a voice
of sanity like Krankor,
well, it's healing, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, God,
I miss him already.
Yeah, me too.
Hold me.
No, Cambot, come on.
Gimme a second here.
We'll be right back.
("MST3K Love Theme" plays)
Man, I feel great.
What a dear man.
Krankor, love him, good guy.
Good people.
No, not the
shrimp paste tanks.
Oh and that was miso soup for
tomorrow's lunch.
Those are very
destructive sand crabs.
Man they got hosed on
the whole barrier deal,
I hope they bought
the service contract.
Clouds of toxic porn
drift across the city.
Let's call our
friends the Koreans.
Oh, no.
The Russians.
The Chinese, oh I guess not.
Strong letter to follow.
Oh darn, is my thing
loose again up there?
Not much traffic today,
you'll have a clear shot
to your stifling workplace
later on, driving to the
bar to avoid your family
should be no problem.
If you lived here
you'd be strafed by now.
Incoming Crispix.
Whoa, hey that wasn't
us, that was the boiler.
Here at WKRP.
My mittens, my mittens,
oh, to hell with it.
Never thought I'd say it,
but suddenly Independence Day
seems a richly nuanced movie.
That reads,
"Welcome Neptunians,
please don't blow us up."
Well, there you have it.
Grandpa tries to set
his digital alarm clock.
Thomas was very
close with Japan
and felt he must resort
to carpet bombing.
Okay guys, let's
lay down that rhythm
track again.
The pierogis of death.
Mr. And Mrs. Bridge!
I feel better.
Shame on you.
Meanwhile, Elliot
Ness and his band
and his cousins and
friends and some guys
he met at the auto parts
store were all on their way
to here.
In the lost city
of Machu Picchu.
I would have to
believe the director
knew this scene wouldn't
be that exciting.
(mumbles)
(panting)
Hey, two little ships, look!
Two little chicks?
What is he, Sinatra?
So they all carpool
to Ground Zero.
Japanese fire drill!
Space Chief's off
having a couple Sapporos
with Jet Jaguar and
Prince of Space.
Ken Kesey's got a gun!
Oh, and now Old
Faithful goes off, great.
I hope that car
doesn't lurch forward!
Go!
The Japanese get so excited
when you take them
to an open field,
they just run around.
N'cest pas, is
that what he said?
N'cest pas?
N'cest pas.
Hey, Space Chief, Space Chief.
Space late.
(cheering)
The doctor dilated my
pupils, can't help ya.
And now enjoy music
from "Triumph of the Will".
♪ Space Chief failed miserably
♪ And tried to
cover up his shame
Time to find a new hero.
It's the Curly gun.
(funny noises)
N'cest pas, n'cest
pas, n'cest pas!
Is that my record?
Okay, great,
we're gonna punch in
on the rhythm track now.
It's a girl, it's
a boy, it's a girl.
Your department of bureaus.
People come on, this way,
I want to pack you
into something,
I don't know what yet.
(explosion)
- Marry me.
- No.
The end.
What, what, what the?
They took out the
Hitler building!
Where's everybody go to
see Hitler memorabilia?
Oh, the Hitler
rides and games,
the Hitler salt
and pepper shakers!
That great restaurant,
The Bunker, it's gone,
you sons of a gun.
You blew it up.
Say Mike, was there
a Hitler building
where you grew up?
Not, no.
Sure.
No.
Space dink.
What next, the Mussolini mall?
Followed by the
Pinochet petting zoo.
Space loser.
And something
blows up somewhere.
We're gonna add
a little reverb
to the harmony there,
alright, here we go.
Our good china.
Prince of Space Chief.
They re-blew up our
building, darn them.
Aha, we didn't want
that building anyway,
we were going to tear
it down, thank you.
Space feeb.
Yeah, this footage.
You know, this is great,
I have such great memories
of this footage.
Yeah, from before?
Yeah, from three times before.
I am starting to get a sense
of Space Chief's ultimate
vulnerability, though.
I think we're going to hear
a deft and poetic
monologue from Space Chief
about his loneliness.
Hi mom, blew up some ships.
I'm getting the
feeling there's some sort
of an air war going on here.
Well, yes, that
is somewhat subtle
and really used as a backdrop,
but I think that theme
is coming through.
No matter how
many he blows up,
there's always three.
He neither adds to nor
subtracts from their numbers.
Yeah, interesting.
Once he crashes
into the ground here
it'll be a typical air show.
Origami!
That's Japanese, right?
I like that.
Well, maybe like is too strong
a word, I don't mind it.
Well actually I hate it, folding
paper, it's stupid, stupid.
Turned on that pretty quick.
Hey look, is there something
under my seat here?
What is that?
What is it?
It's kinda sticky.
Well, don't touch it!
Junior Mint or something?
No, it's bigger than that.
Whoop, something's
going on there.
Oh, we better watch.
New bearing is
minus X6, minus Y10.
These modern clocks,
what the hell time is it?
Minus X6, minus Y10.
Do any of these
kids have names?
They're so distinct,
I don't think there's any
reason to give them names.
Maybe the Japanese
didn't really know
they were making a film, per se.
Maybe they thought
they were working in
a different medium like
fabric sculpture or something.
You know, Space
Chief should really try
going up into space sometime.
Yeah, he's more like
Lower-Atmosphere Chief.
Barely-Off-The-
Stupid-Ground Chief.
(cheering)
Read between the lines, kids.
("MST3K Love Theme" plays)
Look at those
ships, still coming!
There's still some coffee.
Conclusive evidence
that the Japanese
do exist.
Oh man, this movie.
You know, I think
this is gonna become
the Magnificent Ambersons.
In fact, it is the Magnificent
Ambersons right now, it is.
You see it guys, huh?
Don't, don't.
The family riding
in a sleigh, yeah!
There it is, Amberson
mansion, ride into town.
Hot and cold running
water upstairs and down.
It's not working guys,
it's not the
Magnificent Ambersons.
I don't even like the
Magnificent Ambersons!
Servo, Servo, Servo, you're
making it worse.
Movie, see what
you've done to Servo?
End!
This really is disappointing
as the follow up to Psycho.
I'm in here, ow!
We're hit!
Is anyone hurt?
Look, we're on fire!
Where?
It's a liquid oxygen
pocket, get the extinguisher!
Quick, or the
whole place will go!
How bad is it?
Can it be fixed?
Should we cover the tomatoes?
Who Kobe beefed?
It must be Tabana!
Oh, Tabana, thank you,
that clears the whole
thing up, thanks.
That's the linchpin to
the whole dang movie!
Attend to the wounded rocket.
I hit a raccoon!
My ship will take it,
I must move up to 400 feet.
I was just trying
to put the seat back.
You know all he really did
was trick out an Alumacraft.
Believe it or not,
you must fear me.
You know what you guys?
I'm just gonna leave
for a little while.
Mike, Mike.
Air out there.
It's alright.
My Slurpee.
I want my record, damn!
Was that my muffler?
I can't, Tom I'm gonna go
muck out the septic
system or something,
I'll be back at some point.
I'm doing okay,
I'll watch the movie,
I'm doing okay now.
So is this Space Chief?
Oh, you're gone, that's right.
Here, let me do that.
Where have you been?
Hey you guys,
you're gonna miss him
asking where he's been.
Ship heading south
again, approaching us.
I'm lonely now.
I'm ready, don't worry.
I just had to fix my hair.
I'm funny.
Bring all rockets up.
Mrs. F doesn't have any oxygen
out there for us, we
had to come back in.
You okay?
Yeah, fine.
She plays hardball,
doesn't she?
Good morning.
Another day, another dollar.
Now we aim them
at San Francisco,
uh, the Neptune Men.
Yeah, Neptune Men.
Oh, I'm just so glad Japan
honored all those post-war
disarmament treaties, huh?
Now attach rubber bands,
pull back rubber bands.
Carl, we're waiting for you.
Didn't know Estes
was a major defense contractor.
Let's face it, this
is the only thing
mankind has ever done well.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, uh-huh.
That is one major wood tick.
Man, what a boring ride.
Babe Winkelman's
world headquarters.
We've located a bass bearing
south-southwest at two
knots, Mr. Winkelman.
Hey, who snagged all
over the radar screen?
You know, not many movies
can support a full minute
of showing a radar screen.
For example, this one
can't at all, really.
Hey, that guy on the
left, that's an American.
Hey buddy, get out of
the movie, get out,
go run while you can!
Go, sketch, draw
your Snappy the Turtle.
I never get tired of
overhead projection technology.
Locked Christmas
trees at the ready, sir.
Oh boy, there's
a noise I could
listen to all day.
Thanks, movie.
Ten, nine, eight.
Yeah, right, one,
one, one, one, one!
One!
♪ Crying
Actually, the countdown
had more inherent drama
than the rest of the film.
I mean, would he stop, would he
remember the next number?
There goes our
water heater again.
How's the saying go?
"Light and get away?"
We should be able to
get away at this point,
shouldn't we guys?
I'm coming too, just
wait for grandpa rocket.
Well it's the end of
the world as we know it
and actually, I feel
a little bit gassy
but otherwise I'm fine.
Great stock footage,
I'd rather look at
vegetable stock.
Is this any time to shave?
So do either of you guys
know any songs about
stock footage that
can get us through this?
Oh, I know a song
about stock footage,
goes like this.
Eat it movie, take this stupid
little cockroach of a film,
roll it up so tight
and then ram it right up...
Okay, okay, you're
okay, you're okay, it's alright.
He didn't say shields
up please, sir, okay?
I found my record.
Oh no, they survived.
Oh, another nice day.
Thank you, thank
you very much.
For what?
You've done a magnificent job.
I did?
We all did it, together.
Phew.
Thank you muffiny-
haired bachelor.
Due to the apocalypse,
cram school will be delayed
by 45 minutes this morning.
He saved the whole world
with his electro barrier!
Don't be silly.
The alpha electron
rockets did it.
And you worked on them and
shot down the spaceships.
You're great.
You too, kids.
Who am I?
Isn't it great that
Dr. Tanowei got well?
And everything worked out?
One thing, our Space
Chief's gone, too bad, huh?
Oh yeah, I want to
invent a flying car
as fine as the one he drives
and we'll fly it
to Mars and Venus.
Take that back!
You're right, let's
be smart and do it!
I'll make clothes that glow.
Say, let's invent a ray gun.
His tongue.
I dream of something else.
Still insists on
bringing his gum along.
(laughing)
What's left for me then?
You guys invented everything.
I gotta go do 80
off of Donnie Brasco.
Brought to you by the league
of psychotic children.
Surround yourself with annoying,
shrill-voiced children.
Good day.
Freedom.
(clanging vibrations)
Hey, Mike, how you doing?
Oh, hi Servo.
Hey Crow, what you up to?
Well I noticed the
suggestion box was full.
I didn't know we
had a suggestion box.
Oh, well I suggested
that we get one.
Anyway, Mike, I've been
looking at all the suggestions
that I filled the
suggestion box with,
and I couldn't help but notice
that a lot of the suggestions
are for Japan.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah, well here's
one now, look.
Japan, stop making movies.
Yeah, they might wanna
think about that.
That's really good.
Can I read one?
Yeah, Japan, please
reconsider cartoon gun-toting
big-eyed prepubescent blondes
as your national hero.
Pretty good idea.
Grab me one of them bad boys.
Sailor Moon thing
there, yeah, okay.
Dear Japan, maybe it's just
me and the rest of the world,
but huge naked fat men hitting
stomachs is not a sport.
Hey, food for thought
at the very least.
You know Crow, you
don't have to take it out
on the whole country just
'cause you had to sit through
a bad movie.
You know, Mike, not all of
the suggestions are for Japan.
I took the liberty of
penning a suggestion
for Luxembourg.
Here it is, now.
Luxembourg, please get down
on your bony European knees
and thank your lucky stars
every day that you're not Japan.
Crow, now.
Hey, are you Luxembourg?
No.
Then shut up!
Anyway, Luxembourg.
Well, who should I
make this out to, then?
Octavia.
Okay.
It's her birthday.
Oh really?
To Octavia, happy
birthday, love, Mad Goth.
There you go.
Thank you, Mad Goth.
Okay Mike, dig this.
We're gonna grab Bobo
and get out of here,
if we don't have to wait
too damn much longer
in this damn line!
Hey sport, what's your name?
Julius.
Ah, Julius, bet you could
take on a couple lions, huh?
Let's see what you got there.
Whoa, oh boy, hey everybody,
Julius is the new champion.
To Julius, go easy on the
lion, Mad Goth, there you go.
Well hello, fine foxy lady.
Yeah, listen Bobo,
here's the thing--
I'm gonna write down
a room number here.
Okay Bobo, I'm gonna
tell you something,
and then I'm gonna puke,
maybe not in that order.
To the blonde what's
got it going on.
(smashes)
Lawgiver, hello!
Hi, Brain Guy.
They are not gods.
Them, gods?
You gotta be kidding me.
They're no gods and I sure
as hell am no Mad Goth.
Guards, seize them.
("MST3K Love Theme" plays)
Aaah!
What's that?